<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fortune</string>
    <string name="default_quote">Keep Calm and Carry On</string>
    <string name="search_topic">General</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <!--quote based on topic-->
    <!--for information on the setup:https://github.com/TinkersStudio/Fortune/issues/7-->
    <string-array name="art">
        <item>A copy of the universe is not what is required of art; one of the damned
things is ample. — Rebecca West</item>
        <item>A critic is a bundle of biases held loosely together by a sense of taste.
		— Whitney Balliett</item>
        <item>A fool-proof method for sculpting an elephant: first, get a huge block of
marble; then you chip away everything that doesn\'t look like an elephant.</item>
        <item>A man paints with his brains and not with his hands.</item>
        <item>A poet who reads his verse in public may have other nasty habits.</item>
        <item>A true artist will let his wife starve, his children go barefoot, his mother
drudge for his living at seventy, sooner than work at anything but his art.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="general">
        <item>The one charm of marriage is that it makes a life of deception a necessity.
		— Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>"Confound these ancestors.... They've stolen our best ideas!"
		— Ben Jonson</item>
        <item>If you are not careful, you\'re going to catch something.</item>
        <item>Lack of skill dictates economy of style.
		— Joey Ramone</item>
        <item>No one is fit to be trusted with power. … No one. ... Any man who has lived
at all knows the follies and wickedness he\'s capable of. ... And if he does
know it, he knows also that neither he nor any man ought to be allowed to
decide a single human fate.
		— C. P. Snow, The Light and the Dark</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="definitions">
        <item>It isn\'t just a good idea, it\'s the law!</item>
        <item>A weak person who yields to the temptation of denying himself a
	pleasure. - Ambrose Bierce, "The Devil\'s Dictionary"</item>
        <item>Academy:A modern school where football is taught.
Institute: An archaic school where football is not taught.</item>
        <item>Accuracy, n.: The vice of being right</item>
        <item>Adult, n.: One old enough to know better.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="education">
        <item>A fool\'s brain digests philosophy into folly, science into superstition, and
art into pedantry.  Hence University education.
		-- G. B. Shaw</item>
        <item>A good question is never answered.  It is not a bolt to be tightened
into place but a seed to be planted and to bear more seed toward the
hope of greening the landscape of idea.
		-- John Ciardi</item>
        <item>A grammarian\'s life is always in tense.</item>
        <item>A great many people think they are thinking when they are merely
rearranging their prejudices.
		-- William James</item>
        <item>A pencil with no point needs no eraser.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ethnic">
        <item>Aberdeen was so small that when the family with the car went
on vacation, the gas station and drive-in theatre had to close.</item>
        <item>Also, the Scots are said to have invented golf.  Then they had
to invent Scotch whiskey to take away the pain and frustration.</item>
        <item>American by birth; Texan by the grace of God.</item>
        <item>An Englishman never enjoys himself, except for a noble purpose.
		-- A. P. Herbert</item>
        <item>Anything anybody can say about America is true.
        -- Emmett Grogan</item>
        <item>Detroit is Cleveland without the glitter.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="food">
        <item>A gourmet who thinks of calories is like a tart that looks at her watch.
		-- James Beard</item>
        <item>A waist is a terrible thing to mind.-- Ziggy</item>
        <item>Anything is good if it\'s made of chocolate.</item>
        <item>Carob works on the principle that, when mixed with the right combination of
fats and sugar, it can duplicate chocolate in color and texture.  Of course,
the same can be said of dirt.</item>
        <item>Cheese -- milk\'s leap toward immortality.
		-- Clifton Fadiman, "Any Number Can Play\"</item>
        <item>Did you hear that Captain Crunch, Sugar Bear, Tony the Tiger, and
Snap, Crackle and Pop were all murdered recently...

Police suspect the work of a cereal killer!</item>
        <item>Dieters live life in the fasting lane.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="geeky">
        <item>A fail-safe circuit will destroy others.
		-- Klipstein</item>
        <item>A failure will not appear until a unit has passed final inspection.</item>
        <item>A mathematician is a device for turning coffee into theorems.
		-- P. Erdos</item>
        <item>A method of solution is perfect if we can forsee from the start,
and even prove, that following that method we shall attain our aim.
		-- Leibnitz</item>
        <item>A physicist is an atom\'s way of knowing about atoms.
		-- George Wald</item>
        <item>A sine curve goes off to infinity, or at least the end of the blackboard.
		-- Prof. Steiner</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="law"></string-array>
    <string-array name="literature"></string-array>
    <string-array name="love"></string-array>
    <string-array name="kids"></string-array>
    <string-array name="medicine"></string-array>
    <string-array name="pet"></string-array>
    <string-array name="platitude"></string-array>
    <string-array name="politics"></string-array>
    <string-array name="riddle"></string-array>
    <string-array name="sports"></string-array>
    <string-array name="wisdom"></string-array>
    <string-array name="work"></string-array>

</resources>
