<resources>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">265708020488594</string>
    <string name="app_name">Fortune</string>
    <string name="default_quote">Keep Calm and Carry On</string>
    <string name="search_topic">General</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <!--quote based on topic-->
    <!--for information on the setup:https://github.com/TinkersStudio/Fortune/issues/7-->
    <string-array name="art">
        <item>A copy of the universe is not what is required of art; one of the damned
things is ample. — Rebecca West</item>
        <item>A critic is a bundle of biases held loosely together by a sense of taste.
		— Whitney Balliett</item>
        <item>A fool-proof method for sculpting an elephant: first, get a huge block of
marble; then you chip away everything that doesn\'t look like an elephant.</item>
        <item>A man paints with his brains and not with his hands.</item>
        <item>A poet who reads his verse in public may have other nasty habits.</item>
        <item>A true artist will let his wife starve, his children go barefoot, his mother
drudge for his living at seventy, sooner than work at anything but his art.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="general">
        <item>The one charm of marriage is that it makes a life of deception a necessity.
		— Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>"Confound these ancestors.... They've stolen our best ideas!"
		— Ben Jonson</item>
        <item>If you are not careful, you\'re going to catch something.</item>
        <item>Lack of skill dictates economy of style.
		— Joey Ramone</item>
        <item>No one is fit to be trusted with power. … No one. ... Any man who has lived
at all knows the follies and wickedness he\'s capable of. ... And if he does
know it, he knows also that neither he nor any man ought to be allowed to
decide a single human fate.
		— C. P. Snow, The Light and the Dark</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="definitions">
        <item>It isn\'t just a good idea, it\'s the law!</item>
        <item>A weak person who yields to the temptation of denying himself a
	pleasure. - Ambrose Bierce, "The Devil\'s Dictionary"</item>
        <item>Academy:A modern school where football is taught.
Institute: An archaic school where football is not taught.</item>
        <item>Accuracy, n.: The vice of being right</item>
        <item>Adult, n.: One old enough to know better.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="education">
        <item>A fool\'s brain digests philosophy into folly, science into superstition, and
art into pedantry.  Hence University education.
		-- G. B. Shaw</item>
        <item>A good question is never answered.  It is not a bolt to be tightened
into place but a seed to be planted and to bear more seed toward the
hope of greening the landscape of idea.
		-- John Ciardi</item>
        <item>A grammarian\'s life is always in tense.</item>
        <item>A great many people think they are thinking when they are merely
rearranging their prejudices.
		-- William James</item>
        <item>A pencil with no point needs no eraser.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ethnic">
        <item>Aberdeen was so small that when the family with the car went
on vacation, the gas station and drive-in theatre had to close.</item>
        <item>Also, the Scots are said to have invented golf.  Then they had
to invent Scotch whiskey to take away the pain and frustration.</item>
        <item>American by birth; Texan by the grace of God.</item>
        <item>An Englishman never enjoys himself, except for a noble purpose.
		-- A. P. Herbert</item>
        <item>Anything anybody can say about America is true.
        -- Emmett Grogan</item>
        <item>Detroit is Cleveland without the glitter.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="food">
        <item>A gourmet who thinks of calories is like a tart that looks at her watch.
		-- James Beard</item>
        <item>A waist is a terrible thing to mind.-- Ziggy</item>
        <item>Anything is good if it\'s made of chocolate.</item>
        <item>Carob works on the principle that, when mixed with the right combination of
fats and sugar, it can duplicate chocolate in color and texture.  Of course,
the same can be said of dirt.</item>
        <item>Cheese -- milk\'s leap toward immortality.
		-- Clifton Fadiman, "Any Number Can Play\"</item>
        <item>Did you hear that Captain Crunch, Sugar Bear, Tony the Tiger, and
Snap, Crackle and Pop were all murdered recently...

Police suspect the work of a cereal killer!</item>
        <item>Dieters live life in the fasting lane.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="geeky">
        <item>A fail-safe circuit will destroy others.
		-- Klipstein</item>
        <item>A failure will not appear until a unit has passed final inspection.</item>
        <item>A mathematician is a device for turning coffee into theorems.
		-- P. Erdos</item>
        <item>A method of solution is perfect if we can forsee from the start,
and even prove, that following that method we shall attain our aim.
		-- Leibnitz</item>
        <item>A physicist is an atom\'s way of knowing about atoms.
		-- George Wald</item>
        <item>A sine curve goes off to infinity, or at least the end of the blackboard.
		-- Prof. Steiner</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="law">
        <item>A countryman between two lawyers is like a fish between two cats.
		-- Ben Franklin</item>
        <item>A friend of mine won\'t get a divorce, because he hates lawyers more than he
hates his wife.</item>
        <item>A jury consists of twelve persons chosen to decide who has the better lawyer.
		-- Robert Frost</item>
        <item>According to Kentucky state law, every person must take a bath at least
once a year.</item>
        <item>And then there was the lawyer that stepped in cow manure and thought
he was melting...</item>
        <item>Anti-trust laws should be approached with exactly that attitude.</item>
        <item>Atlanta makes it against the law to tie a giraffe to a telephone pole
or street lamp.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="literature">
        <item>A horse!  A horse!  My kingdom for a horse!
		-- Wm. Shakespeare, "Richard III"</item>
        <item>"... all the modern inconveniences ..."
		-- Mark Twain</item>
        <item>All things that are, are with more spirit chased than enjoyed.
		-- Shakespeare, "Merchant of Venice"</item>
        <item>Always the dullness of the fool is the whetstone of the wits.
		-- William Shakespeare, "As You Like It"</item>
        <item>An honest tale speeds best being plainly told.
		-- William Shakespeare, "Henry VI"</item>
        <item>As flies to wanton boys are we to the gods; they kill us for their sport.
		-- Shakespeare, "King Lear"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="love">
        <item>A career is great, but you can\'t run your fingers through its hair.</item>
        <item>Absence in love is like water upon fire; a little quickens, but much
extinguishes it.
		-- Hannah More</item>
        <item>All the passions make us commit faults; love makes us commit the most
ridiculous ones.
		-- La Rochefoucauld</item>
        <item>A kiss is a course of procedure, cunningly devised, for the mutual
stoppage of speech at a moment when words are superfluous.</item>
        <item>Always there remain portions of our heart into which no one is able to enter,
invite them as we may.</item>
        <item>Don\'t despair; your ideal lover is waiting for you around the corner.</item>
        <item>Falling in love is a lot like dying.  You never get to do it enough to
become good at it.</item>
        <item>Give me chastity and continence, but not just now.
		-- St. Augustine</item>
        <item>Hearts will never be practical until they can be made unbreakable.
		-- The Wizard of Oz</item>
        <item>His heart was yours from the first moment that you met.</item>
        <item>I don\'t want people to love me.  It makes for obligations.
		-- Jean Anouilh</item>
        <item>I love you, not only for what you are, but for what I am when I am with you.
		-- Roy Croft</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="kids">
        <item>A baby is an alimentary canal with a loud voice at one end and no
responsibility at the other.</item>
        <item>A kid\'ll eat the middle of an Oreo, eventually.</item>
        <item>Adopted kids are such a pain -- you have to teach them how to look like you ...
		-- Gilda Radner</item>
        <item>Any father who thinks he\'s all important should remind himself that this
country honors fathers only one day a year while pickles get a whole week.</item>
        <item>Are you a parent?  Do you sometimes find yourself unsure as to what to
say in those awkward situations?  Worry no more...</item>
        <item>Because we don\'t think about future generations, they will never forget us.
		-- Henrik Tikkanen</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="medicine">
        <item>Anyone who goes to a psychiatrist ought to have his head examined.
		-- Samuel Goldwyn</item>
        <item>Death has been proven to be 99% fatal in laboratory rats.</item>
        <item>Dental health is next to mental health.</item>
        <item>God is dead and I don\'t feel all too well either....
		-- Ralph Moonen</item>
        <item>"Good health" is merely the slowest rate at which one can die.</item>
        <item>Happiness is good health and a bad memory.
		-- Ingrid Bergman</item>
        <item>Health is merely the slowest possible rate at which one can die.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pet">
        <item>Anyone who considers protocol unimportant has never dealt with a cat.
		-- R. Heinlein</item>
        <item>Breeding rabbits is a hare raising experience.</item>
        <item>Cats are intended to teach us that not everything in nature has a function.
		-- Garrison Keillor</item>
        <item>Cats are smarter than dogs.  You can\'t make eight cats pull a sled through
the snow.</item>
        <item>Cats, no less liquid than their shadows, offer no angles to the wind.</item>
        <item>Chihuahuas drive me crazy.  I can\'t stand anything that shivers when it\'s warm.</item>
        <item>Does the name Pavlov ring a bell?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="platitudes">
        <item>A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush.
		-- Cervantes</item>
        <item>A bird in the bush usually has a friend in there with him.</item>
        <item>A bird in the hand makes it awfully hard to blow your nose.</item>
        <item>A chicken is an egg\'s way of producing more eggs.</item>
        <item>A chronic disposition to inquiry deprives domestic felines of vital qualities.</item>
        <item>A closed mouth gathers no foot.</item>
        <item>A farmer is a man outstanding in his field.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="politics">
        <item>A Difficulty for Every Solution.
		-- Motto of the Federal Civil Service</item>
        <item>A diplomat is a man who can convince his wife she\'d look stout in a fur coat.</item>
        <item>A free society is one where it is safe to be unpopular.
		-- Adlai Stevenson</item>
        <item>A government that is big enough to give you all you want is big enough
to take it all away.
		-- Barry Goldwater</item>
        <item>A great empire, like a great cake, is most easily diminished at the edges.
		-- B. Franklin</item>
        <item>A great nation is any mob of people which produces at least one honest
man a century.</item>
        <item>A national debt, if it is not excessive, will be to us a national blessing.
		-- Alexander Hamilton</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sports">
        <item>Ever feel like life was a game and you had the wrong instruction book?</item>
        <item>Every creature has within him the wild, uncontrollable urge to punt.
		-- Snoopy</item>
        <item>Football is a game designed to keep coalminers off the streets.
		-- Jimmy Breslin</item>
        <item>Horse sense is the thing a horse has which keeps it from betting on people.
		-- W. C. Fields</item>
        <item>How can you think and hit at the same time?
		-- Yogi Berra</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wisdom">
        <item>A clash of doctrine is not a disaster -- it is an opportunity.</item>
        <item>A lifetime isn\'t nearly long enough to figure out what it\'s all about.</item>
        <item>A priest advised Voltaire on his death bed to renounce the devil.
Replied Voltaire, "This is no time to make new enemies."</item>
        <item>A thing is not necessarily true because a man dies for it.
		-- Oscar Wilde, "The Portrait of Mr. W. H."</item>
        <item>All hope abandon, ye who enter here!
		-- Dante Alighieri</item>
        <item>An idea is not responsible for the people who believe in it.</item>
        <item>Beauty is one of the rare things which does not lead to doubt of God.
		-- Jean Anouilh</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="work">
        <item>A committee is a group that keeps the minutes and loses hours.
		-- Milton Berle</item>
        <item>A company is known by the men it keeps.</item>
        <item>A commune is where people join together to share their lack of wealth.
		-- R. Stallman</item>
        <item>A continuing flow of paper is sufficient to continue the flow of paper.
		-- Dyer</item>
        <item>A man is known by the company he organizes.
		-- Ambrose Bierce</item>
        <item>A meeting is an event at which the minutes are kept and the hours are lost.</item>
        <item>A motion to adjourn is always in order.</item>
        <item>A verbal contract isn\'t worth the paper it\'s written on.
		-- Samuel Goldwyn</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="humorist"></string-array>

</resources>
